Finding Aid for the Donald Kalish Papers LSC.0578
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Bill of Rights newsletter, undated (Box 125, Folder 6)
- Set the Date campaign memo (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- Set the Date campaign leaflet for petition (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 8)
- Set the Date campaign newspaper clipping (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 9)
- Set the Date campaign leaflet on Ellsberg (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 10)
- Information about the Set the Date campaign sent to faculty, 1971 November (Box 125, Folder 11)
- Set the Date campaign Teachers' Committee (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 12)
- Set the Date campaign Faculty Union Project (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 13)
- Set the Date campaign UCLA teach-in (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 14)
- Set the Date campaign (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 15)
- Set the Date campaign Indochina fact sheet(Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 16)
- Set the Date campaign legislative position (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 17)
- Set the Date campaign brochure and notes (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 18)
- Set the Date campaign correspondence (Fall), 1971 (Box 125, Folder 19)
- Newsletter: "Dissent and Disorder: A Report to the Citizens of Chicago on the April 27 Peace Parade", undated (Box 125, Folder 20)
- Indochina Information Project newspaper clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 125, Folder 21)
- Newspaper clippings on UCLA Center Study of Violent Behavior, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 22)
- Set the Date campaign and anti-war newspaper clippings (Fall), 1971 (Box 126, Folder 1)
- Set the Date campaign correspondence (Fall), 1971 (Box 126, Folder 2)
- National Action Group proposal, meetings, and correspondence, 1970 (Box 126, Folder 3)
- National Peace and Justice Conference, People's Peace Treaty, undated (Box 126, Folder 4)
- War Resisters League calendar, 1967-1968 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- War Resisters League calendar, "Days of Civil Disobedience", 1970-1971 (Box 126, Folder 6)
- War Resisters League calendar, "Days of Gandhi", 1969-1970 (Box 126, Folder 7)
- Movement literature by Commager, Mulherin, Magison, Wald, and Shoup, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1)
- University Committee on Vietnam: Deposits receipts, contributions, and acknowledgments, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 2)
- University Committee on Vietnam: Formation of ad hoc committee, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 3)
- University Committee on Vietnam: Thursday meetings (Spring), 1966 (Box 127, Folder 4)
- Pertaining to May 28th event, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 5)
- Drinan and Kendal correspondence, 1981 August (Box 127, Folder 6)
- Concerned Faculty: Thank you letters, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 7)
- Concerned Faculty: Member list, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 8)
- Concerned Faculty, 1982 February (Box 127, Folder 9)
- Concerned Faculty, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 10)
- University Committee on Vietnam: First meeting (Spring), 1968 (Box 127, Folder 11)
- University Committee on Vietnam: November 14 meeting, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 12)
- University Committee on Vietnam: April and May meetings, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 13)
- University Committee on Vietnam, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 14)
- University Committee on Vietnam: Fall and winter newspaper clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 127, Folder 15)
- University Committee on Vietnam (Summer), 1966 (Box 127, Folder 16)
- Merit raise, Kalish, newspaper clippings, 1970-1975 (Box 127, Folder 17)
- Equal education adverts, petitions, and newspaper clippings, 1969 March (Box 127, Folder 18)
- Resolution draft for December Senate meeting on Angela Davis, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 19)
- Concerned Faculty: Newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 127, Folder 20)
- Southern Conference Education Fund newsletter, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 21)
- Department of Motor Vehicles, 1948-1955 (Box 127, Folder 22)
- Donald Kalish's medical history, 1952 (Box 127, Folder 23)
- Blackjack strategy notes, undated (Box 127, Folder 24)
- Kalish's merit raise notes and correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 127, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1964-1992 (Box 127, Folder 26)
- University Committee on Vietnam: Financial records and correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 128, Folder 1)
- Valley Peace Center activities and meetings, newsletter, brochure, 1968-1969 (Box 128, Folder 2)
- Vietnam Day Committee financial records, 1966-1968 (Box 128, Folder 3)
- Veterans for Peace in Vietnam newspaper clipping, 1967-1968 (Box 128, Folder 4)
- Vietnam GI newspaper clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 128, Folder 5)
- Quaker Action Group correspondence and clippings, 1969 (Box 128, Folder 6)
- Quaker Peace and social action newsletter and brochure, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 7)
- Ad hoc committee for spring mobilization, UCLA campus, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 8)
- Spring mobilization San Francisco office, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 9)
- Spring mobilization March 21 meeting minutes, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 10)
- Spring mobilization post-March meeting, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- St. Patrick's witness, 1967 June (Box 129, Folder 1)
- Student mobilization newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Student Mobilization Committee correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Student mobilization newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
- Woody Guthrie: A Life, Joe Klein, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- November 11th Convocation: Threat of nuclear war slide list, undated (Box 129, Folder 6-7)
- "Quine's Natural Deduction System for Quantification Theory," lectures, 1952 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Ditto material 184A (Spring), 1955 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 184A: Sentential Logic (Spring), 1955 (Box 130, Folder 3)
- Natural deduction and tautology, undated (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 184A: Syllabus (Spring), 1956 (Box 130, Folder 5)
- Notes for lecture on classical full system, undated (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 184A: Predicate calculus (Spring), 1955 (Box 130, Folder 7)
- Completeness of predicate calculus (Spring), 1955 (Box 130, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 184A: Deduction theory (Spring), 1956 (Box 130, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 184A: Problem set (Spring), 1955 (Box 130, Folder 10)
- Stencils for MT2, undated (Box 130, Folder 11)
- 184A Metatheorem III (Spring), 1956 (Box 130, Folder 12)
- Extra mimeograph sheets 0184 (Spring), 1956 (Box 130, Folder 13)
- "Completeness of Sentential Logic: Rosser's Proof," 184A (Spring), 1956 (Box 130, Folder 14)
- "Natural Deduction for Predicate Calculus and Proof of Its Adequacy", undated (Box 130, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 184A: Lecture notes (Spring), 1956 (Box 130, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 184A: Student problems (Spring), 1956 (Box 130, Folder 17)
- Calculus validity and completeness, 1958 (Box 130, Folder 18)
- Philosophy 184B: Syllabus (Spring), 1960 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 184B: Syllabus, proofs and lectures on CN-calculus (Spring), 1960 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 184B: Proving strong specification from weak (Spring), 1960 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 184B: Syllabus (Spring), 1960 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 184B: Stencils and quantifier logic, 1960 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 184B: Stencils and CN-calculus (Spring), 1960 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 184B: Final exams (Spring), 1959 (Box 131, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 184B: Montague (Spring), 1964 (Box 131, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 184B: Final exams and reports (Spring), 1963 (Box 131, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 184B: Ditto masters and extra copies, 1960-1963 (Box 131, Folder 10)
- Set theory, Davis, 1969 October (Box 131, Folder 11)
- "On Huntington's axioms for Algebra of Logic", undated (Box 131, Folder 12)
- Schutte's system of deduction, undated (Box 131, Folder 13)
- Montague's model theory seminar (Spring), 1963 (Box 131, Folder 14)
- Evert W. Beth, completeness of predicate calculus and proofs, 1952 March 27 (Box 131, Folder 15)
- Skolem normal formal logic supplementary material, undated (Box 131, Folder 16)
- Logic, independence, and proof, undated (Box 131, Folder 17)
- Deduction theorem, undated (Box 131, Folder 18)
- Godels completeness proof, undated (Box 131, Folder 19)
- On the foundations of mathematics, undated (Box 131, Folder 20)
- Natural deduction system for sentential calculus, undated (Box 131, Folder 21)
- Lower-order predicate calculus, 1948 (Box 131, Folder 22)
- Uniform quantification theory lecture based on Quine's methods, 1952-1954 (Box 131, Folder 23)
- Undecidability proof of first order logic, revision of Quine's church theorem, undated (Box 131, Folder 24)
- Quine's mathematical logic, notes by Kalish and Kelly, 1948-1949 (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 184: Formalization of SC, 1952-1954 (Box 132, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 184: Rule of replacement, 1952-1954 (Box 132, Folder 3)
- "Some Theorems in the Theory of Descriptions," Frege Russell, undated (Box 132, Folder 4)
- Pat Britt, some logic, undated (Box 132, Folder 5)
- Aristotelian logic, Cohen, Nagel, and Eaton, undated (Box 132, Folder 6)
- Syllabus for Cooley's primer, Paul Marhenke, undated (Box 132, Folder 7)
- 0-31 Swarthmore, Cooley, 1946-1947 (Box 132, Folder 8)
- Logic 31, Quine's methods and notes (Fall), 1950 (Box 132, Folder 9)
- Cooley, solutions to problems, special attention to descriptions, undated (Box 132, Folder 10)
- Proofs from PM, undated (Box 132, Folder 11)
- Notes on PM, and the theory of logical types, undated (Box 132, Folder 12)
- Notes on Hilbert, Ackermann, and Bernays, undated (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Principal mathematics, undated (Box 133, Folder 2)
- Woman-spirit, Moving Toward Peace and Justice calendar, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 3)
- "The Unraveling of Nuclear Arms Treaties," The Defense Monitor, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 4)
- UCAM Network News: "United Campuses to Prevent Nuclear War", 1987 January (Box 133, Folder 5)
- Alliance for Survival, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 6)
- Forum West Steering Committee meeting, 1986 December 20 (Box 133, Folder 7)
- Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1986 December (Box 133, Folder 8)
- Women's International League of Peace and Freedom, 1986 December 15 (Box 133, Folder 9)
- El Rescate, 1986 November (Box 133, Folder 10)
- Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation, 1987-1988 (Box 133, Folder 11)
- Activity guidelines at UCLA on services and facilities regulation, 1984 (Box 133, Folder 12)
- American Friends Service Committee, 1986 November 21 (Box 133, Folder 13)
- US-El Salvador Conference: In Search of Peace, 1986 November (Box 133, Folder 14)
- National security, undated (Box 133, Folder 15)
- Student programming, undated (Box 133, Folder 16)
- United Campuses to Prevent Nuclear War, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 17)
- SAGE-UAW newspaper clippings, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 18)
- Newsletters, articles, and correspondence, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 19)
- Newspaper clippings on Black Panthers, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Huggins and Clark newspaper clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 2)
- Angela Davis Newsweek article, 1970 October 26 (Box 134, Folder 3)
- Dismissal of Clark Kerr newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings related to Ronald Reagan, 1965-1967 (Box 134, Folder 5)
- Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1965-1966 (Box 134, Folder 6)
- Government of colleges and universities, 1965-1967 (Box 134, Folder 7)
- The draft and anti-brass, 1967-1970 (Box 134, Folder 8)
- Newspaper clippings on Angela Davis, 1969-1972 (Box 135, Folder 1)
- Assorted newspaper clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 135, Folder 2)
- Kalish's testimony for Chicago Conspiracy Trial, 1970 January 9 (Box 135, Folder 3)
- Vietnam newspaper clippings, 1968 (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings on campus unrest, 1969 (Box 135, Folder 5)
- Assorted newspaper clippings, 1969 (Box 135, Folder 6)
- Newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 1-3)
- Newspaper clippings on Angela Davis case, 1969-1973 (Box 136, Folder 4)
- Coalition for Economic Survival, 1975-1978 (Box 136, Folder 5)
- Freedom to Read Foundation, 1973-1978 (Box 136, Folder 6)
- Understanding China newsletter, 1973-1978 (Box 137, Folder 1)
- Referendum projects, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 2)
- Republicans Against Reagan, undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
- Friends Committee on National Legislation, "Visit Your Congressman", 1966-1967 (Box 137, Folder 4)
- War Resisters League, 1967-1973 (Box 137, Folder 5)
- SANE, 1970-1973 (Box 137, Folder 6)
- SANE, 1968-1970 (Box 138, Folder 1)
- Sunflower County Improvement Association, 1968-1969 (Box 138, Folder 2)
- Dissenting Democrats, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 3)
- Electoral process post-primary, 1968 (Box 138, Folder 4)
- McCarthy: Kaufman paper, 1968 (Box 138, Folder 5)
- McCloskey: Republican peace candidate vs. Keating and Shirley Temple, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 6)
- Peace and Freedom Party, 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 7)
- Political candidates Calderon, Hannon, and McCarthy (Spring), 1968 (Box 138, Folder 8)
- National Conference for New Politics, 1968 (Box 138, Folder 9)
- New politics and Julian Bond, 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 10)
- Californians for an Alternative in November, 1968 August (Box 138, Folder 11)
- Council for a Livable World, 1967-1969 (Box 138, Folder 12)
- Californians for Liberal Representation, 1968 (Box 138, Folder 13)
- California Democratic Council, 1967-1968 (Box 138, Folder 14)
- Newspaper clippings on prison issue, 1971 (Box 139, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 150B: Student projects, 1971 March (Box 139, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 150B: Final exams, 1971 March (Box 139, Folder 3)
- Carolyn Ferkel project and exam, 1971 March (Box 139, Folder 4)
- Newspaper clippings and photographs of Isla Vista ROTC burning (Winter), 1971 (Box 139, Folder 5)
- "Confrontation at Cornell," Life magazine article, 1969 June (Box 140, Folder 1)
- "The Multiversity: Crucible of the New Working Class," Carl Davidson, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 2)
- On prison regulations, undated (Box 140, Folder 3)
- "Diana Oughton's Story: Making of a Terrorist," Lucinda Franks and Thomas Powers, 1970 (Box 140, Folder 4)
- "Where the Fuse On That Dynamite Leads," I.F. Stone, 1970 March 23 (Box 140, Folder 5)
- "Radical Bombers," by Andrew Kopkind, and "Lonely Terrorist," by Irving Howe, 1970 (Box 140, Folder 6)
- "Student Revolts, Student Movement," Walter Laqueur, 1966-1970 (Box 140, Folder 7)
- Scranton report on student unrest, I.F. Stone, 1970 October (Box 140, Folder 8)
- "Degrading Education," by Robt. Klawitter, and "The Laying On Of Culture," by John McDermott, undated (Box 140, Folder 9)
- Campus unrest article in Science, undated (Box 140, Folder 10)
- Philsophy 150B: Final projects and exams (Winter), 1971 (Box 140, Folder 11)
- Papers (Spring), 1971 (Box 140, Folder 12)
- Judy Powers, "People's Treaty and May Action: An Evaluation", 1971 February 20 (Box 140, Folder 13)
- David Strick, The TEP House, undated (Box 140, Folder 14)
- Newspaper clippings, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 15)
- Kissinger and the Vietnam negotiations, 1969 January (Box 140, Folder 16)
- Loren Kleinrock and John Rimeney exams (Winter), 1971 (Box 140, Folder 17)
- Newspaper clippings on prison issues, 1969-1971 (Box 140, Folder 18)
- Disorientation (NUC), 1969-1970 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- "The Case for Abolishing ROTC", 1969 (Box 141, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 150B: Exams and papers (Winter), 1971 (Box 141, Folder 3)
- Indochina war information packet, 1970-1971 (Box 141, Folder 4)
- The Atlantic, 1971 March (Box 141, Folder 5)
- Educational material on Vietnam from Bud (Summer), 1971 (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Regents' resolution to fire Angela Davis and court decision, 1969 (Box 141, Folder 7)
- "On Student Power," Guenter Lewy and Stanley Rothman, undated (Box 141, Folder 8)
- "Conceptions of the University," by Martin Trow, undated (Box 141, Folder 9)
- "On Columbia," Rudd and Greeman, 1969 (Box 141, Folder 10)
- "The Tangled Asian Web," by Russell Johnson, 1965 November (Box 141, Folder 11)
- Congressional record, why Vietnam, 1965-1967 (Box 141, Folder 12)
- Committee on Foreign Relations reports on Vietnam, 1964-1969 (Box 141, Folder 13)
- "New American Militarism," David Schoup ABC speech, 1967-1969 (Box 141, Folder 14)
- "On Getting Out of Vietnam," Clark Gifford in Life magazine, 1970 (Box 141, Folder 15)
- Treatment of prisoners at Soledad, 1970 July (Box 141, Folder 16)
- Phillip Burton's speech on appropriation for Vietnam War, 1967 March 2 (Box 141, Folder 17)
- Clipping on Vietnam War, 1966 March (Box 141, Folder 18)
- "What Must the University Be?" by Douglas F. Dowd, undated (Box 141, Folder 19)
- "An Open Letter to Barry Goldwater," by Karl Hess, undated (Box 141, Folder 20)
- "The Death of Politics," by Karl Hess, undated (Box 141, Folder 21)
- "Confessions of a Right-wing Liberal," by Murray N. Rothbard, undated (Box 141, Folder 22)
- Berrigans court case newspaper clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 141, Folder 23)
- "Neutrality of the Universities: Columbia and the Warfare State," Gadfly, undated (Box 141, Folder 24)
- Harvard alumni bulletin on Dow Chemical sit-in, 1967 November (Box 141, Folder 25)
- TA's schedules and handouts (Winter), 1971 (Box 141, Folder 26)
- "The Penal Code: Its Failure to Rehabilitate" by Rosalie Leodoro (Winter), 1971 (Box 142, Folder 1)
- "Aspects of Higher Education" by Steve Stemerman, 1971 March (Box 142, Folder 2)
- Arthur Ryskind, on academic freedom conduct, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
- Steve Weinberg on academic freedom conduct, undated (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 150B: Exams and papers (Winter), 1971 (Box 142, Folder 5)
- Jacquelyn Takeda on academic freedom conduct, undated (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Jim Browder on neutrality of the university (Winter), 1971 (Box 142, Folder 7)
- Lydia Garrison on prisons and prisoners (Winter), 1971 (Box 142, Folder 8)
- "New Morning-Changing Weather. Statement from the Underground White Student Left", undated (Box 142, Folder 9)
- Fact sheets on Vietnam, Laos, and Cambodia, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 10)
- Magazine articles on Vietnams, 1967 (Box 142, Folder 11)
- "Laos, Nixon and the CIA" by Peter Dale Scott, 1970 April 9 (Box 142, Folder 12)
- "The Vietnamization of Laos" by Banning Garrett, 1970 June (Box 142, Folder 13)
- "Anatomy of a Coup" by T.D. Allman, 1970 April 9 (Box 142, Folder 14)
- "Cambodia: Nixon's Trap" by Franz Schurmann, 1970 June 1 (Box 142, Folder 15)
- "The Indochina War" by Walter LaFeber, 1970 May (Box 142, Folder 16)
- Political crimes exam and paper, Deborah Hornback (Winter), 1971 (Box 142, Folder 17)
- Channeling from the Selective Service orientation kit, 1965 July 1 (Box 142, Folder 18)
- About the constitution, National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 142, Folder 19)
- "Cambodia: The Administration's Version and the Historical Record" by George McT. Kahin, 1970 May 17 (Box 142, Folder 20)
- Bay Area Institute newsletter, 1972 (Box 142, Folder 21)
- "Vietnam: A Thousand Years of Struggle" by Terry Cannon, 1969 (Box 142, Folder 22)
- "The American Involvement in Vietnam" by George McT. Kahin, 1970 May (Box 142, Folder 23)
- Philosophy 150B: Papers (Winter), 1971 (Box 142, Folder 24)
- Dave Dellinger on China, Cuba, and Vietnam, 1964-1967 (Box 142, Folder 25)
- "Mission to Cambodia" by Russell Johnson, 1966 (Box 142, Folder 26)
- "The Earth Belongs to the People: Ecology and Power", 1970 (Box 142, Folder 27)
- Rapid transit (Summer), 1970 (Box 142, Folder 28)
- Newspaper clippings on prison system, 1971 June 14 (Box 142, Folder 29)
- Philosophy 150B: Grade and course info (Winter), 1971 (Box 142, Folder 30)
- "Academic Freedom, Educational Objectives, and the Secondary School" by Loren Kleinrock and John Rimeney (Winter), 1971 (Box 143, Folder 1)
- Robert Ramirez and Stephen Baldocchi on student power (Winter), 1971 (Box 143, Folder 2)
- Debra Shane and Diane Tucker on political vs. non-political prisoners, 1971 February (Box 143, Folder 3)
- David Lees and Ken Dale, Academic freedom and campus newspapers, undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
- Academic Senate material on student participation, 1969-1970 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Professor Savage's resolution to the Academic Senate on abolishing ROTC, 1969 May 13 (Box 143, Folder 6)
- Faculty conduct codes and materials academic freedom, 1970-1971 (Box 143, Folder 7)
- Newspaper articles: Fischler, Eisenberger, and Ludwin on political repression, 1968-1971 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- Lauby, Zola, and Kirk on educational system, undated (Box 143, Folder 9)
- "Meet Me in St. Louis?" by Louis Gilden, 1970-1971 (Box 143, Folder 10)
- "Experts Reply to Critics" on teach-ins, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 11)
- "The Responsibility of Intellectuals" by Noam Chomsky, 1967 February (Box 143, Folder 12)
- "Persons and Punishment" by Herbert Morris, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 13)
- Hitch on student unrest and UC resolutions, 1970 (Box 143, Folder 14)
- "Academic Freedom" School of Law, Duke University, Vol. XXVIII, No. 3 (Summer), 1963 (Box 143, Folder 15)
- "Can It Happen Here?" by Philip Green and "Are Radical Students Fascistic?", 1970 September 20 (Box 143, Folder 16)
- Congressional visits by concerned faculty, 1984-1985 (Box 143, Folder 17)
- Correspondence with Congress, Berman and Hamilton, 1986-1987 (Box 143, Folder 18)
- Concerned Faculty newsletters, 1970-1997 (Box 143, Folder 19)
- Letters to and from Concerned Faculty members, 1991-1993 (Box 143, Folder 20)
- Concerned Faculty Congress and president, 1986-1990 (Box 143, Folder 21)
- Concerned Faculty event "Let the People Decide" and newspaper clippings, 1984 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Concerned Faculty minutes and correspondence, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations (Winter), 1989 (Box 144, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 031: Course evaluations, 1995 March (Box 144, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations and records (Winter), 1988 Winter (Box 144, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations, 1973 (Box 144, Folder 6)
- Course/instructor evaluations, biographies, and abstracts, 1977-1978 (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations (Spring), 1997 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations (Fall), 1970 (Box 145, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 031: Course evaluations (Fall), 1972 (Box 145, Folder 4)
- "Foresight" An Undergraduate Journal of Philosophy, Vol. I, No. 1 (Spring), 1997 (Box 145, Folder 5)
- Notes on letters of recommendation, undated (Box 145, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations (Spring), 1997 (Box 145, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 031: Course comments (Winter), 1995 (Box 145, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations (Winter), 1973 (Box 145, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 135: Course evaluations (Spring), 1974 (Box 145, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 134: Course evaluations (Winter), 1969 (Box 145, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 031: Course evaluations (Spring), 1969 (Box 145, Folder 12)
- Two cards and thank you note, 1989-1991 (Box 145, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations (Winter), 1991 (Box 145, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 032: Course evaluations (Winter), 1990 (Box 146, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 032: Comments, Warren correspondence, and Dean's comments, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 2)
- Card from students (Spring), 1989 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 032: Evaluations and Julia Phillips note (Winter), 1988 (Box 146, Folder 4)
- Tarski's set theory and proofs, T620-T628 (Ordinals), undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
- Tarski's set theory and proofs, T200-T375, undated (Box 146, Folder 6)
- Tarski's set theory and proofs, T30-T78 calculus sets, undated (Box 146, Folder 7)
- Notes from Tarski on list of theorems, 1952-1953 (Box 146, Folder 8)
- Tarski's set theory and proofs, T120-T199, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 9)
- Tarski's set theory and proofs, T79-T119 infinite operations and order couples, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 10)
- Set theory, copy not corrected (Spring), 1991 (Box 146, Folder 11)
- Tarski's set theory, Mates notes, materials on Montague's assault (Spring), 1953 (Box 146, Folder 12)
- Tarski axioms and proofs, T1-T27, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 13)
- Tarski's set theory and proofs, T555-T617, 1952 (Box 146, Folder 14)
- Tarski's set theory and proofs, T376-T539, undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
- Hans Meyerhoff, 1990 November (Box 147, Folder 2)
- Set theory, 1954 (Box 147, Folder 3)